gocdkeys.com 2018-06-30

# PRIVACY AND DATA PROTECTION AGREEMENT

### Who is responsible of your data?

  * Owner: Overthings, S.L. (“GOCDKEYS”)
  * Company ID (CIF): B57925703
  * Address: Carrer dentol 3 bajos, Palma de Mallorca, 07610, Balearic Islands, Spain
  * Email: soporte@gocdkeys.com

### What is GOCDKEYS?

GOCDKEYS provides a video game and gaming products price comparison service that helps Customers compare and buy games and gaming products at best prices.

GOCDKEYS gathers several sites specialized in the price comparison of video games and gaming products.

  * Gocdkeys.com
  * Gocdkeys.it
  * Gocdkeys.pt

Security & Privacy is an important part of our platform that we take very seriously. Therefore, this Privacy Policy governs the manner in which GOCDKEYS website collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users of all the gocdkeys websites mentioned above. This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products or services offered by GOCDKEYS.

In order to ensure confidentiality and lawful processing of its, Visitors, Customers and comparison price websites users personal data, GOCDKEYS in its capacity of a data controller and of a processor, conducts its activities in strict compliance with the requirements set in the Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of this data (GDPR).

This Privacy Policy applies to all Customers, GOCDKEYS Users and Visitors of our Sites and Services.

### What information do we collect and how do we use it?

We may collect the following types of information about you on our websites:

  * Customers and Visitors of our sites: We collect your personal data in the following ways
    * **Sign up form:** When you click on sign up button or log in, you will be able to sign up as a new user under our websites. We collect your username, email and password in order to offer you the possibility to save preferences regarding currency, language and price alerts. We also use this information to earn tickets in order to get products for free or send, occasionally, newsletters to your email address.
    * **Personal data form:** When you win a product through our giveaways or wheel of fortune, you will have to fill up the personal data form in order to send you the product you won, so we will ask you to provide us with your name, surname, date of birth (for age verification), address and country. You can access to this form from: https://gocdkeys.com/en/user/personaldata
    * We also collect website’s user data:
      * To administer our Website and for internal operations, including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research, statistical and survey purposes;
      * To write or display content such as case studies or comments and reviews on our site;
      * To allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so;
  * **Technical, Usage and Location Information:** We automatically collect information on how you interact with the Site, such as the IP address from which you access the Site, date and time, information about your browser, operating system and computer or device, pages viewed and items clicked. We may also collect location information, including location information automatically provided by your computer or device. We use cookies and similar technologies to collect some of this information and persist your login to our site. We collect this information to improve the results and user experience within our sites, and display the content that better fit with you.
  * **Third Party Platforms:** We may collect information when you interact with our advertisements and other content on third-party sites or platforms, such as social networking sites. This may include information such as Facebook Likes, profile information gathered from social networking sites during signup or the fact that you viewed or interacted with our content.

GOCDKEYS may use third party service providers to help us operate our business or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or collecting website analytics. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.

GOCDKEYS engages certain onward sub processors that may process personal data submitted to GOCDKEYS services. These sub processors are listed below, and may be updated by GOCDKEYS from time to time:

  * Google Analytics
  * Mailchimp
  * G2APay
  * Steam
  * Twitter
  * Facebook
  * Google

### Social logins

GOCDKEYS also allows websites users to connect social accounts to your profile. GOCDKEYS users that have a social login enabled on their profile will be able to see basic information related to the connected accounts. This includes but is not limited to your name, email address, social profile URL’s and associated profile picture.

GOCDKEYS will only ever use information that you have made public or specifically allowed us to access when you accept permissions. GOCDKEYS does not know or store any passwords associated with your social accounts.

GOCDKEYS does not track or provide any personal information to companies until you explicitly provide consent. This means that you do not expose any personal information to other companies.

### Cookies

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

GOCDKEYS use Cookies to track information about users in order to serve them content. This includes but is not limited to:

  * Persist Customers sessions that are logged into GOCDKEYS Websites.
  * Tracking and awarding tickets for referring users via our reward program.
  * Tracked users referred by our referral program.

### Third party websites

Users may find advertising or other content on our site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

### Legal Disclosures

In certain limited circumstances, we may also have to disclose your personal data to public authorities and other third parties, if the disclosure is in response to lawful requests made by such public authorities, including to conform with national security or law enforcement requirements. Your personal information may also be disclosed to other third parties when compelled to do so by government authorities or required by law or regulation including, but not limited to, in response to court orders and subpoenas.

GOCDKEYS may also share personal data with third parties to prevent, investigate or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our Terms of Service or any other agreement related to the Services, or as otherwise required by law.

### Information security

We use appropriate technical and organizational security measures to protect any personal information we process about visitors to our website against unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction. However, please note that no Internet transmission can ever be guaranteed 100% secure, and so we encourage you to take care when disclosing personal information online and to use readily available tools, such as Internet firewalls, secure e-mail and similar technologies to protect yourself online.

EU and EEA residents

The servers where GOCDKEYS stores all personal data are located in the European Union. If you are located in a country member of either the EU or the EEA, please be aware that any information provided to us, including personal information, will be transferred from your country of origin to the EU. Except in the case of data transfers under the EU-US Privacy Shield and the Swiss-US Privacy Shield, we may ask for your express consent to provide such data to us or allow us to collect such data.

### International transfer of personal data

All personal data we process is stored directly, without any subsequent transfers, on EU-based servers, which we loan from datacenter that is certified and adheres to the EU – U.S GDPR.

To additionally guarantee to our Customers and their European users (data subjects) the legality of our processing services and the international transfers of the personal data, GOCDKEYS has undertaken GDPR compliant contractual commitments, binding us, as a data processor, to protect the data privacy and to ensure the most adequate level of data security.

Please note that the country where we operate may have privacy and data protection laws that differ from, and are potentially less protective than, the laws of your country. You agree to this risk when you create an account with us and click “I accept GOCDKEYS Terms of Service & Privacy Policy” to data transfers, irrespective of which country you live in. If you later wish to withdraw your consent, you can delete your GOCDKEYS account directly on you profile page.

### Data retention periods

GOCDKEYS will not retain data longer than is necessary to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected or as required by applicable laws or regulations. For Campaign data, GOCDKEYS Users have control of the purpose for collecting data, and the duration for which the Personal Data may be kept. When a User’s account is terminated, deleted or expired, all Personal Data collected through the platform will be deleted, as required by applicable law.

### Privacy controls & Choices

GOCDKEYS Websites Communication: Our Customers, Site Visitors and Users have a choice about how we use their personal data to get in touch with them and may choose to opt-out at any time by unsubscribing or changing their account settings.

Newsletter Users Notifications: We provide an easy mechanism for opt-ing out of any communication from campaigns inside the Post Entry Email. You can simply selec the Unsubscribe links in the footer.

Users Social Accounts: We provide a mechanism for every users to remove any linked social accounts from GOCDKEYS via the Profile page.

Your Rights: We provide all Customers, Visitors and Users of our sites with the opportunity to request access, correction, restriction, deletion, data portability or oppose to any personal information that has previously been provided to us in connection with the use of our website, as required by law. You can send us an email to support@gocdkeys.com. We may request specific information from you to confirm your identity.

### Gocdkeys data protection officer

GOCDKEYS has a Data Protection Officer who is responsible for matters relating to privacy and data protection. This Data Protection Officer can be reached at the following address:

  * Overthings, S.L. Carrer dentol 3 bajos, Palma de Mallorca, 07610, Balearic Islands, Spain.
  * Mail: Support@gocdkeys.com

### Compliance with children´s online privacy protection act

Because the nature of our Site and Services does not appeal to children under the age of 13, GOCDKEYS does not knowingly acquire or receive personal data from children under 13. We do not intentionally process any information, including Personal Data, from children or other individuals who are not legally able to use our site and Services. If we later learn that any user of our service is under the age of 13 and that we have obtained his/her personal data, we will promptly delete it from our database and will take further steps to restrict that individual from future access to our services, unless we are legally obligated to retain such data.

If you are a parent or legal guardian of a child under 13 and believe that we might have any information from or about such child, please contact us at the email or mailing address provided at the end of this Privacy Policy.

### Business transfers

In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, customer information is typically one of the business assets that are transferred. Moreover, if GOCDKEYS, or substantially all of its assets were to be acquired, or in the unlikely event that GOCDKEYS goes out of business, customer information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquire of GOCDKEYS or its assets may continue to use your Personal Information as set forth in this policy.

### Changes to this privacy policy

GOCDKEYS has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

### Your acceptance of these terms

By using this site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and terms of service. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our site. Your continued use of the site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

### Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at support@gocdkeys.com

This document was last updated on May 24th, 2018
